Guide to the NYU Abu Dhabi Campus Posters Collection AD.RG.002.2
NYU Abu Dhabi, Archives and Special Collections
NYU Abu Dhabi Campus Posters Collection
2014-Present
NYU Abu Dhabi, Archives and Special Collections
AD.RG.002.2
6.25 Linear Feet in 4 legal size document boxes, 3 oversize boxes, and 3 folders in oversize map case drawer.
Scope and Contents
The NYU Abu Dhabi University Archives Campus Poster Collection has been compiled by NYU Abu Dhabi Archives and Special Collections staff from a variety of sources. The collection consists of posters and flyers publicizing various campus events, such as lectures, performances, exhibitions, cultural evenings, campaigns, and other activities in the community. Dates of the physical posters start at 2018, while some of the digital copies are from as early as 2014.
The collection is arranged into two series.
Series 1 is an accummulating collection of posters gathered by Archives and Special Collections staff during routine walks of the campus. Materials have been collected from bulletin boards, elevators, and other spaces of promotion as activities have ended. Arranged chronologically by academic years and semesters within, this series aims to provide a snapshot of campus life activities each semester.
Series 2 is a collection of Student Interest Group (SIG) and Student Activities events announcements, digitally downloaded by Archives and Special Collections staff from various spaces of student communication and exchange, such as Facebook groups, and the OrgSync and Engage platforms. This series is arranged alphabetically by SIG or Student Program.
Conditions Governing Access
Collection is open.
Related Materials
Materials related to the Campus Posters Collection include NYUAD Publications and Ephemera [RG 002.1], Records of NYU Abu Dhabi Student Interest Groups and Student Activities [RG 009.3.1], and the Student Life Events Photos [AD.RG.009.3-2-1].
Universities; Printed Materials; New York University Abu Dhabi; Posters
- Physical Posters Collection, 2018-Ongoing; 5.25 Linear Feet in 3 document boxes, 2 oversize boxes, and 3 folders in oversize map case drawer.
  Scope and Contents
  This collection of posters is comprised of posters gathered across campus spaces such as bulletin boards and inside elevators. Some posters may have also been donated from time to time by campus community members and integrated into this series.
  - Campus Posters, 2018 - Spring 2019 (Box Box 1)
    Arrangement
    When known, campus posters are arranged by month/year. Posters with unknown dates are filed in "general" folders.
  - Campus Posters, Spring 2019-Spring 2020 (Box Box 2)
  - Campus Posters, 2020-2022 (Box Box 3)
  - Campus Posteres, 2023 - (Box Box 4)
  - Campus Posters (oversize), 2018 (Oversize Box 1)
  - Campus Posters (oversize), 2019-2022 (Oversize Box 2)
  - Campus Posteres (oversize), 2023 - (Oversize Box 3)
  - Campus Posters (oversize), 2018 - 2023 (Map-case 1.c)
- Digital Posters Collection, 2013-2018; 351 Megabytes Folders and Subfolders organized by SIG (Box Electronic Records, Folder SIG Posters_2014-2018)